Going to work can be a slog, especially if your job is full of tedious tasks and pointless meetings.
上班可能是件苦差事，尤其是如果你的工作满是单调乏味的任务和毫无意义的会议。
Obviously, work is necessary to earn an income, and if you get good job satisfaction it’s a bonus!
显然，工作是为了赚钱谋生，而如果能获得良好的工作满足感，那就是额外的收获了！
But what can make it more worthwhile are the extra perks that your employer offers you as a reward for your loyalty and commitment.
但能让这份工作更有价值的，是雇主为了奖励你的忠诚度和奉献精神而提供的额外福利。
Employee benefits are commonplace these days.
如今，员工福利已经很普遍了。
Traditionally, these have included a good pension and extra days off work.
按照传统，这些福利包括丰厚的养老金和额外的休假天数。
But when a job used to be for life, there wasn’t much incentive to try and keep staff.
但在过去，一份工作往往是终身制的，雇主没有太大动力去努力留住员工。
Now millennials look to leave their jobs within the first two years, and when they are seeking a position, they want to know the benefits they’ll get on top of their pay.
现在，千禧一代往往在入职头两年就想离职，而且他们找工作时，除了薪水，还想知道能获得哪些福利。
These include half-price cinema tickets, cycle to work schemes and gym passes.
这些福利包括半价电影票、骑行上班计划和健身卡。
But these perks come at a cost to an employer, and now technology is being used to discover if and when they offer value for money.
但这些福利对雇主来说是有成本的，如今，企业正利用技术来判断这些福利是否和何时物有所值。
Writing for the BBC, Jessica Bown says “Emerging technologies such as data analytics, chatbots, and wearables can help employers know which benefits resonate with employees.”
杰西卡·鲍恩在为英国广播公司撰写的文章中表示：“数据分析、聊天机器人和可穿戴设备等新兴技术，能帮助雇主了解哪些福利能引起员工的共鸣。”
The idea is to avoid wasting money on things that don’t get used and enable a company to tailor what it can offer to attract and retain the right staff.
其目的是避免在无人使用的福利上浪费资金，同时让公司能够定制福利内容，以吸引和留住合适的员工。
As an example, at merchant bank, Close Brothers, AI has been used to develop chatbots that can help employees to find information on subjects ranging from mental health to saving for retirement at any time.
例如，在商业银行克洛斯兄弟集团（Close Brothers），人工智能被用于开发聊天机器人，员工可以通过这些机器人随时查询从心理健康到退休储蓄等各类信息。
And Microsoft has developed software to help businesses track their employee’s wellbeing needs.
微软也开发了相关软件，帮助企业跟踪员工的健康需求。
Anna Rasmussen, founder of Open Blend, told the BBC “It shows companies what their employees need to stay motivated and reach their full potential in real-time.”
Open Blend公司创始人安娜·拉斯穆森向英国广播公司表示：“它能实时向公司展示员工需要什么来保持积极进取、发挥全部潜力。”
Insurance company Vitality offer wearable technology to track employees’ movements. Staff can earn ‘rewards’ by having their activity tracked.
保险公司维塔力（Vitality）提供可穿戴技术来追踪员工的活动情况，员工的活动数据被记录后可以获得“奖励”。
A study found that by measuring participant’s performance, they did the equivalent of 4.8 extra days of activity per month.
一项研究发现，通过对参与者的表现进行量化，他们每月的活动量相当于增加了4.8天。
It seems that if used in the right way, technology can provide greater engagement between an employee and the company. That can lead to a happier, healthier and committed work force.
看来，如果使用得当，技术可以加强员工与公司之间的联系，进而打造一支更快乐、更健康、更忠诚的员工队伍。
But human resources experts warn against relying solely on tech for deciding on employee benefits provision.
但人力资源专家警告称，不应仅仅依靠技术来决定员工福利的提供。
Greater understanding of new technology and how it’s used is needed, they say.
他们表示，需要更深入地了解新技术及其使用方式。